https://www.rag-bone.com/privacy-policy.html

Sign Up
*The promo code will be sent to the e-mail address entered.
Effective Date: June 2020
Rag & Bone Holdings, LLC and its subsidiary and affiliate companies, including Rag & Bone Industries, LLC (collectively, “rag & bone,” “Us,” “Our” or “We”) and recognize the importance of protecting the information collected about them. This Privacy Policy addresses the use and disclosure of personal information we collect from you.
By visiting this Web site, or providing your information to us, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Please exit this Web site immediately if you do not accept this Privacy Policy or are accessing the Web site in a country or other territory where use of the Web site is not permitted.
What Information Does rag & bone Collect?
Rag & bone collects and stores information from visitors to this Web site, including those who register their information or who use the online store. For example, when you place an order, we collect and store some or all of the following information that you provide: name, billing address, shipping address, email address, telephone number, credit card number and expiration date. This information is used to provide the products and services that you have ordered or requested, to process and ship orders, to send order and shipping confirmations and to provide customer service. This information also may be used for our own marketing and internal business purposes, and to contact you about sales, special offers and new site features, unless you have opted not to receive promotional communications in connection with this Web site. To serve you better, we may combine information you give us with other information which is publicly available.
We may collect and store certain other information automatically whenever you interact with this Web site. For example, we may collect your IP address, browser information and reference site domain name every time you visit this Web site. We also may collect information regarding customer traffic patterns and site usage. This information is used to analyze and improve this Web site and to provide our customers with a fulfilling shopping experience.
Also, like many web sites, we use “cookies,” which are files stored on your computer's hard drive by your browser. We use cookies to ascertain which web pages are visited and how often, to make our Web site more user friendly, and to give you a better experience when you return to the Web site. For example, cookies allow us to save your password so you do not have to re-enter it every time you visit our Web site. Most browsers accept cookies automatically but allow you to disable them. We recommend that you leave cookies “turned on” so that we can offer you a better shopping experience on this Web site. Please note that our third party advertising providers may also use cookies to gather information about your web viewing activities. Please see below for more information about our third party advertising providers and how to opt out of targeted advertising.
How We Use Your Information
Whenever you give us your personal information we will use it in accordance with applicable privacy laws and for the purposes set out in this policy, on the data entry forms you complete, in any relevant terms and conditions and on pages or emails which link to the data entry forms.
We may use the information we collect to deliver the products and Services you request, to maintain and customize your account and our interactions with you (such as on our digital properties), and to provide, maintain, and improve our Services. We also use the information we collect to:
·
Create and manage your online accounts and profiles;
·
Communicate with you about our Services, including to tell you about products and services that may be of interest to you;
·
Complete the transactions you request, perform our contractual obligations, and use as otherwise anticipated within the context of our ongoing business relationship;
·
Respond to your requests, inquiries, comments, and suggestions;
·
Facilitate your engagement with the Services, including to enable you to post comments and reviews, to engage with other customers, and to post on social media;
·
Offer contests, sweepstakes, loyalty programs or other promotions;
·
Personalize your online experience and the advertisements you see when you use the Services or third-party platforms based on your preferences, interests, purchasing history and browsing behavior;
·
Monitor, audit and analyze trends, usage, and activities in connection with our Services;
·
Carry out short-term activities and other internal uses related to the products or services you purchase from us or your ongoing relationship with us;
·
Conduct internal research and development;
·
Detect, investigate, and respond to security incidents and protect against illegal or objectionable activities, including the unauthorized use of the Services, and protect the rights and property of Glossier and others;
·
Debug, identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality of our Services;
·
Comply with our legal obligations, including those required for you to benefit from rights recognized by law, or any regulatory requirements or provisions; and
·
Conduct or administer surveys and other market research.
How is My Information Used for Targeted Advertising?
We work with third parties that use their own technologies to provide tailored advertisements on our behalf across the Internet. During your visit to this web site, those third parties may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect information, such as, but not limited to, click stream information, your IP address, and time and date. This information may be used to analyze and track data as well as provide advertisements that may be of interest to you. Additional information about third-party advertising and opting out of having your browsing information used for advertising purposes can be found at www.networkadvertising.org.
For more information about interest-based ads, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used for interest-based advertising purposes, please visit www.aboutads.info/choices. European users may opt out of receiving targeted advertising through the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance.
We may also work with third parties to serve ads to you as part of a customized campaign on third-party platforms (such as Facebook or Google). As part of these ad campaigns, we or third-party platforms may convert information about you, such as your email address, into a unique value that can be matched with a user account on these platforms to allow us to learn about your interests and to serve you advertising that is customized to your interests. Note that the third-party platforms may offer you choices about whether you see these types of customized ads.
Is Information Collected From Children?
This Web site is not intended or directed to anyone under the age of 13. We do not sell or ship any items ordered through this Web site directly to anyone who we know to be under the age of 13, nor do we collect any personal information from anyone who we know to be under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, you should use this Web site only with the involvement of a parent or guardian and should not submit any personal information to us.
Your Rights and Choices
Managing or deactivating your rag & bone account
You may review, update, or modify your account information, including profile, contact, payment and shipping information, at any time by logging into your rag & bone account. You may also deactivate your rag & bone account by emailing privacy@rag-bone.com.
Opting out of email marketing
You may unsubscribe from our promotional emails at any time by following the instructions included in those emails. If you opt out of receiving such communications, note that we may continue to send you non-promotional emails (such as order confirmation emails or emails about changes to our legal terms).
Cookies and Interest- Based Advertising
You may stop or restrict the placement of Technologies on your device or remove them by adjusting your preferences as your browser or device permits. The online advertising industry also provides websites from which you may opt out of receiving targeted ads from data partners and other advertising partners that participate in self-regulatory programs. You can access these and learn more about targeted advertising and consumer choice and privacy, at www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp, http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/, https://youradchoices.ca/choices/, and www.aboutads.info/choices/. To separately make choices for mobile apps on a mobile device, you can download DAA’s AppChoices application from your device’s app store. Alternatively, for some devices you may use your device’s platform controls in your settings to exercise choice.
Please note you must separately opt out in each browser and on each device. Advertisements on third party websites that contain the AdChoices link may have been directed to you based on information collected by advertising partners over time and across websites. These advertisements provide a mechanism to opt out of the advertising partners’ use of this information for interest-based advertising purposes. For more information about how we use cookies, please read our cookie policy.
Text/SMS Message Consent And Opt-Out
If you choose, you can provide your mobile phone number to receive Text Message alerts from us to receive product and/or event information, promotional offers and more. You agree that by providing your mobile phone number you expressly consent to receive automated marketing Text Messages from us to the mobile phone number provided. These messages may use information automatically collected based on your actions while on our sites and may prompt messaging such as cart reminders.  To the extent you voluntarily opt to have SMS notifications sent directly to your mobile phone, we receive and store the information you provide, including your telephone number or when you read a text message. Consent is not required to purchase goods or services.
You can opt out from further text marketing communications at any time by texting “STOP” to our text messages.
Web Push Notifications/Alerts
With your consent, we may send promotional and non-promotional push notifications or alerts to your browser. You can deactivate these messages at any time by changing the notification settings on your browser.
European Residents
If you are a European Resident, defined for the purposes of this Privacy Policy to include residents of the European Economic Area, United Kingdom and Switzerland, you have certain rights and protections under the law regarding the processing of your personal data.
Legal Basis for Processing
If you are a European Resident, we process your personal data when:
·
We need to use your personal data to perform our responsibilities under our contract with you (e.g., processing payments for and providing the rag & bone products you have ordered).
·
We have a legitimate interest in processing your personal data. For example, we may process your personal data for performance marketing activities, to conduct data analytics and to provide, secure, and improve our Services.
·
We need to do so to comply with a legal obligation to which we are subject.
·
We need to do so to protect your vital interests or those of others.
·
We have your consent to do so, which you may withdraw at any time.
Data Subject Requests
If you are a European Resident, you have the right to access personal data we hold about you and to ask that your personal data be corrected, updated, or erased. You may also have the right to object to, or request that we restrict, certain processing. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, you may contact us as indicated below. If you have a rag & bone account, you may also review, update, and delete certain personal data by logging into your account.
Questions or Complaints
If you are a European Resident and have a concern about how we process personal data that we are not able to resolve, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the data privacy authority where you live. For contact details of your relevant local Data Protection Authority, please see http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm or, if you are a resident of Switzerland, https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/en/home/the-fdpic/contact/.
Your California Privacy Rights
California Consumer Privacy Act:
This section provides details about rights afforded to California residents under the California Consumer Privacy Act (or "CCPA"), and supplemental details about the personal information we collect about California residents.
In the last 12 months, we collected the following categories of personal information: identifiers (such as name, contact information and device identifiers); commercial information (such as items purchased); internet or other network activity information (such as browsing behavior and other usage data); location data; inferences (such as purchasing preferences); demographic data (such as gender); electronic, visual or similar information (such as customer support call information); professional or employment-related information (such as in resumes you provide); and other personal information (such as product feedback or payment method information). For more details about the personal information we collect, including the categories of sources, please see the What information does rag & bone collect section above. We collect this information for the business and commercial purposes described in the HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION & DOES RAG & BONE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH OTHERS sections above. We share this information with the categories of third parties described in the HOW IS MY INFORMATION USED FOR TARGETED ADVERTISING section above.
Subject to certain limitations, the CCPA provides California residents the right to request to access to details about the categories or specific pieces of personal information we have collected in the last 12 months (including about information we disclosed for a business purpose), to request to delete their personal information, to opt out of any sales that may be occurring, and to not be discriminated against for exercising these rights.
We do use third-party cookies and related technologies to send targeted ads and this may be deemed a "sale" under the CCPA. To opt out of these "sales," please visit the following page Do Not Sell My Personal Info.
California residents may make request access or deletion requests by emailing us at privacy@rag-bone.com. We will verify your request by asking you to provide information that matches information we have on file about you. You can also designate an authorized agent to exercise these rights on their behalf, but we will require proof that the person is authorized to act on your behalf and may also still ask you to verify your identity with us directly.
We will not discriminate against you for exercising your rights. This generally means we will not deny you goods or services, charge different prices or rates, provide a different level of service or quality of goods, or suggest that you might receive a different price or level of quality for goods. Please know, if you ask us to delete or stop selling your data, it may impact your experience with us, and you may not be able to participate in certain programs or membership services which require usage of your personal information to function.
To exercise the California privacy rights described above, please write us at privacy@rag-bone.com or call us toll free at +1-844-RAG-BONE (724-2663) 8am to 11pm ET, 7 days a week.
Your California Privacy Rights — Shine the Light:
If you are a California resident, California law permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information by rag & bone to third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes within the immediately preceding calendar year. Rag & bone will provide you with a list of the categories of personal information disclosed and a list of the names and addresses of the third parties. To make such a request, please write us at privacy@rag-bone.com.
Privacy Policy Updates
We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Whenever we make a change, we will post the updated policy at this Web site and we encourage you to check our policy periodically. If we make a material change to this Privacy Policy that would lessen your privacy rights, we will either continue to honor our prior policy for information that we collected when it was in force, or we will ask for your consent to the change. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@rag-bone.com or write to us at the following address:
Rag & Bone
E-Commerce Department
425 W.13th Street
New York, NY 10014
Get first access to new products and promotions.
Your Email
Your Zip Code
Customer Care
Customer Care
Contact Us
Your Order
Shipping
Returns
©2020 rag & bone
Need some help? Chat with us.
Our chat is currently available from 8am to 11pm EST To chat with one of our service representatives please click the button below.
start chat
Offline
Our chat is currently unavailable. Please come back between the hours of 8am to 11pm EST to chat with one of our representatives.
How can we help you?
Please find some helpful links below. Customer Care available 8 am - 11 pm EST.
help@rag-bone.com
844.724.2663
Live Chat
Track your Package
Shipping
Returns
Size Guides
Customer Care
Get first access to new products, promotions, and other special announcements.
Receive 15% Off Your First Order When You Sign Up*
Submit
*The promo code will be sent to the e-mail address entered.
International shipping available to more than 75 countries
We are working with our global partner Borderfree to offer you the best possible international shopping experience.Please select the country you would like to ship to and your currency below:
Country:
Currency:
United Arab Emirates Dirham (AED)
Netherlands Antillan Guilder (ANG)
Australian Dollar (AUD)
Bosnian Convertible Mark (BAM)
Barbados Dollar (BBD)
Taka (BDT)
Bulgarian Lev (BGN)
Bahraini Dinar (BHD)
Boliviano (BOB)
Brazilian Real (BRL)
Bahamian Dollar (BSD)
Belize Dollar (BZD)
Canadian Dollar (CAD)
Swiss Franc (CHF)
Chilean Peso (CLP)
Yuan Renminbi (CNY)
Colombian Peso (COP)
Costa Rican Colon (CRC)
Czech Koruna (CZK)
Danish Krone (DKK)
Dominican Peso (DOP)
Egyptian Pound (EGP)
Euro (EUR)
British Pound (GBP)
Quetzal (GTQ)
Hong Kong Dollar (HKD)
Lempira (HNL)
Croatian Kuna (HRK)
Hungarian Forint (HUF)
Israeli Shekel (ILS)
Indian Rupee (INR)
Jamaican Dollar (JMD)
Jordanian Dinar (JOD)
Japanese Yen (JPY)
Riel (KHR)
Korean Won (KRW)
Kuwaiti Dinar (KWD)
Cayman Islands Dollar (KYD)
Tenge (KZT)
Lebanese Pound (LBP)
Sri Lanka Rupee (LKR)
Moroccan Dirham (MAD)
Rufiyaa (MVR)
Mexican Peso (MXN)
Malayan Ringgit (MYR)
Namibia Dollar (NAD)
Cordoba Oro (NIO)
Norwegian Krone (NOK)
Nepalese Rupee (NPR)
New Zealand Dollar (NZD)
Omani Rial (OMR)
Balboa (PAB)
Peruvian Nuevo Sol (PEN)
Philippine Peso (PHP)
Pakistan Rupee (PKR)
Polish Zloty (PLN)
Guarani (PYG)
Qatari Riyal (QAR)
New Romanian Leu (RON)
Russian Ruble (RUB)
Saudi Riyal (SAR)
Swedish Krona (SEK)
Singapore Dollar (SGD)
Lilangeni (SZL)
Thai Baht (THB)
Turkish Lira (TRY)
Taiwan Dollar (TWD)
Ukraine Hryvnia (UAH)
US Dollar (USD)
Uruguay New Peso (UYU)
CFA Franc BEAC (XAF)
CFA Franc BCEAO (XOF)
South African Rand (ZAR)
Start Shopping
Are you shipping to the U.S.?
Please click here to shop our U.S. site
Returning Customers
If you are a registered user, please enter your email and password.
Create an Account
Creating an account is simple and makes your future shopping visits easier.
Sign up is free: You can access your account from anywhere.
Quicker checkout: Easy checkout process with your information already saved.
Address book: Save shipping addresses for yourself, friends or family in your personal address book.
Create an Account
Your cart is empty
Checkout
View Cart
